Alexandra Campbell - AKA
Ali. Designer gone full
stack web developer.

Dedicated programmer coming from a background in industrial design and graphics. I

love scripting digital experiences for people and can offer a range of both creative and technical skills. Always ready to work with any new tools for the job.

## CONTACT

Ali Campbell 1+ (602) 625-2503 AlexandraBrinnCampbell@gmail.com



### DEV

JavaScript • React • Enzyme • jQuery • HTML5 • CSS/Sass • Bootstrap • Node.js • Ruby on Rails • SQL • PostgreSQL • MVC architecture • OOP • git • GitHub • Heroku

#### UX & UI

Webflow • Invision • Adobe Creative Suite • Sketch • Figma • Whimsical • Mindnode • AutoCad • user interviews & testing • branding & creative content

## **EDUCATION**

MAY 2019 - CURR

Thinkful. JavaScript, Node Fullstack Engineering Program

**JAN - MAR 2019** 

Le Wagon, London. Ruby on Rails Coding Bootcamp

FEB - MAR 2018

General Assembly 8 week course in UX design

**BDES INDUSTRIAL DESIGN, 2007** 

**Emily Carr University, Vancouver BC** 

#### **PROJECTS**

# Doctors Near Me | killeraliens.github.io/doctors-near-me

Doctors Near Me is an app that locates and displays medical professionals based on your location, insurance plan, or specialty search inputs. This project utilizes OOJS & constructor functions to pull doctor info from highly nested JSON objects, as well as ES 2017 features to sequence multiple API calls for its filter results.

Duilt with HTML5, CSS, jQuery, JavaScript, Better Doctor API, Google Maps JavaScript API, Google Geocoding and Reverse Geocoding APIs

## Goat's Guide | www.goatsguide.com

Goat's Guide is a heavy metal event & venue database concept as well as an ongoing study in UX design. I am currently reworking this project using React, Express/Node to reduce app loading time, and encourage user participation with the integration of Facebook's Graph API.

Current version is built with Ruby on Rails, and utilizes HTML-scraping gems such as Watir and Nokogiri, along with custom background tasks/Sidekiq to collect event data. Uses Devise gem for authentication. PostgreSQL database. Deployed with Heroku.

You can find more projects on my website at killeraliens.github.io/alexandra-brinn

### **EXPERIENCE**

APR 2015 - JUL 2018

## Burgeon Group | Design Project Manager | instagram @BurgeonGroup

Burgeon group is a niche design & build firm with a stellar international reputation for the concept, design, and fabrication of children's experience in the public library space. My role as design project manager included coordination between client, design, and fabrication departments. I worked closely with the CEO/lead designer contributing to client communications, design, and marketing, as well as executed the technical drafting, construction & installation plan documents for our inhouse fabrication teams.

2012 - 2015

## Demi Coffee | instagram @DemiCoffee

Developed and operated a small food & beverage concept with a partner. Great experience in customer service, creative offerings, fun with branding. Best cold brew.

2012 - CURRENT

## Curiotile

Personal project in product design. Iterative flatpack designs in stainless and powedercoat steel, custom displays & storage solutions. Website coming soon.

2009 - 2013

## Ah Diós | Freelance Graphics & Branding

Collaborating with three others in web, film, and UX backgrounds. Brand development and various projects in graphic, signage, web, and packaging for Visual+Intent, Cartel Coffee Lab, Request Manufacturing, Sooh Media +